http://nordiskadental.se/privacy-policy/

Loading... (0%)
Privacy Policy
Processing of Company Information and Personal Data (GDPR)
What is GDPR?
GDPR is the General Data Protection Regulation and an EU regulation that replaces previous national legislation on the handling of personal data. Personal data means any kind of information that can be linked to a living natural person. Personal data should not be confused with general corporate information that is linked to a legal entity. The GDPR is valid from 25 May 2018 and covers all EU member states, including Norway, belonging to the European Economic Area (EEA). Non-EU companies that handle personal data about EU citizens are covered by the legislation.
Openness
We at Nordiska Dental AB protect you as a customer, which means that we always collect company information and personal information responsibly and with regard to your integrity. For us, it’s important to be open with what data we collect and how we use it.
Freedom of choice
You are always entitled to inform and change incorrect business information and personal data, to object to our use of personal data and the right to have personal data erased. All provided that we as the so-called Personal data controller thus does not violate legal requirements or impedes our ability to live up to agreements or agreements entered into.
Why do we collect data?
We collect company information and personal data in order to comply with the entered customer agreement and due to legal requirements that are related to our sales, as well as our obligations under accounting and tax legislation. We also collect company information and personal data for information and marketing purposes. All in order to communicate, among other things, the right information to the right person in your organization by telephone, mail or e-mail, and for delivering ordered goods.
What data do we collect?
We collect company information and personal information that you send to us, so when you become a customer and place orders with us, enter into an agreement with us, contact our support or customer service, fill out forms on our website, reply to e-mail, or looking for a job with us. We also collect data from external sources, for example via company and address registers, and when visiting our website. Since we mainly cooperate with you as an entrepreneur in the dental sector, we mainly collect general business information such as company name, organization number, phone number and address. These are not personal data (unless you engage in private business) and are not covered by GDPR. We also collect certain personal information, such as name, email and phone number.
How do we use collected information?
Collected data is used for information and marketing purposes, in the notification of future deliveries, in the delivery management of ordered goods and when we invoice. Collected information is also used to comply with legal requirements and agreements entered into, which includes the provision of product information including safety data sheets and any information about product recall.
Responsibility
By collecting personal information, we are as organization so-called personal data controller. This means, among other things, that we will protect personal data against unauthorized treatment and against loss, destruction or accidental injury. We never sell personal data to third parties. In some cases, we share the necessary company and personal data to the partner to ensure high quality and security in, for example, freight forwarders for the delivery of ordered goods, notification of future delivery (for transport administrator), invoicing (to invoice administrator).In all cases where we share personal information, we have established so-called personal data agreement that governs the partner’s rights and obligations. Your company information and your personal information are safe with us. As a rule, we save company information and personal data associated with you and the company you represent as long as it is required to fulfill the above purposes or as long as we are required by law to do so.
If you have any further questions about our processing of company information and personal data, please contact us at Nordiska Dental.
